<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LitongLab</title>
    <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LitongLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.litonglab.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TACK</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: TACK
[Github] [Video and Slides] Abstract
The shared nature of the wireless medium induces contention between data transport and backward signaling, such as acknowledgement. The current way of TCP acknowledgment induces control overhead which is counter-productive for TCP performance especially in wireless local area network (WLAN) scenarios. In this paper, we present a new acknowledgement called TACK (&amp;ldquo;Tame ACK&amp;rdquo;), as well as its TCP implementation TCP-TACK. TCP-TACK works on top of commodity WLAN, delivering high wireless transport goodput with minimal control overhead in the form of ACKs, without any hardware modification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: ART
[Github] [A demo application] Abstract
Packet losses significantly impact the user experience of wide-area applications such as content distribution and remote procedure call (RPC) based services. However, our production network measurement studies show that the legacy loss recovery is far from satisfactory due to the wide-area loss characteristics (i.e., dynamics and burstiness) in the wild. In this paper, we propose a sender-side Adaptive ReTransmission scheme, ART, which minimizes the recovery time of lost packets with minimal redundancy cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blender</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Blender
[Github] [A demo application] Abstract
In the widely used Bluetooth Low-Energy (BLE) neighbor discovery, the parameter configuration of neighbor discovery directly decides the results of the trade-off between discovery latency and power consumption. Therefore, it requires evaluating whether any given parameter configuration meets the demands. The existing solutions, however, are far from satisfactory due to unsolved issues.
Blender, a simulation framework that produces a determined and full probabilistic distribution of discovery latency for a given parameter configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FiND</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: FiND
[Github] Abstract
FiND is a novel neighbor discovery protocol that accelerates BLE neighbor discovery via Wi-Fi fingerprints without any hardware modifications. The design rationale of FiND is that the two modes of WiFi and BLE show complementarity in both wireless interference and discovery pattern. When abstracting the neighbor discovery problem, this demonstration provides validation for the approach of reasoning-based presence detection in the real world.
Reference
Tong Li, Bowen Hu, Guanjie Tu, Jinwen Shuai, Jiaxin Liang, Yukuan Ding, Ziwei Li, Ke Xu: Accelerating BLE Neighbor Discovery via Wi-Fi Fingerprints.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>