<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LitongLab</title>
    <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LitongLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.litonglab.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TACK</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: TACK
[Github] 
[Video and Slides] 
Abstract
The shared nature of the wireless medium induces contention between data transport and backward signaling, such as acknowledgement. The current way of TCP acknowledgment induces control overhead which is counter-productive for TCP performance especially in wireless local area network (WLAN) scenarios. In this paper, we present a new acknowledgement called TACK (&amp;ldquo;Tame ACK&amp;rdquo;), as well as its TCP implementation TCP-TACK. TCP-TACK works on top of commodity WLAN, delivering high wireless transport goodput with minimal control overhead in the form of ACKs, without any hardware modification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ART</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: ART
[Github] 
[A demo application] 
Abstract
Packet losses significantly impact the user experience of wide-area applications such as content distribution and remote procedure call (RPC) based services. However, our production network measurement studies show that the legacy loss recovery is far from satisfactory due to the wide-area loss characteristics (i.e., dynamics and burstiness) in the wild. In this paper, we propose a sender-side Adaptive ReTransmission scheme, ART, which minimizes the recovery time of lost packets with minimal redundancy cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blender</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Blender
[Github] 
[A demo application] 
Abstract
In the widely used Bluetooth Low-Energy (BLE) neighbor discovery, the parameter configuration of neighbor discovery directly decides the results of the trade-off between discovery latency and power consumption. Therefore, it requires evaluating whether any given parameter configuration meets the demands. The existing solutions, however, are far from satisfactory due to unsolved issues.
Blender, a simulation framework that produces a determined and full probabilistic distribution of discovery latency for a given parameter configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FiND</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: FiND
[Github] 
Abstract
FiND is a novel neighbor discovery protocol that accelerates BLE neighbor discovery via Wi-Fi fingerprints without any hardware modifications. The design rationale of FiND is that the two modes of WiFi and BLE show complementarity in both wireless interference and discovery pattern. When abstracting the neighbor discovery problem, this demonstration provides validation for the approach of reasoning-based presence detection in the real world.
Reference</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AutoRec</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/autorec/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/autorec/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: AutoRec
Abstract
Due to the limited permissions for upgrading dual-side (i.e., server-side and client-side) loss tolerance schemes from the perspective of CDN vendors in a multi-supplier market, modern large-scale live streaming services are still using the automatic-repeat-request (ARQ) based paradigm for loss recovery, which only requires server-side modifications. In this paper, we first conduct a large-scale measurement study with up to 50 million live streams. We find that loss shows dynamics and live streaming contains frequent on-off mode switching in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transhub</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/transhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/transhub/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Transhub
Abstract
Transhub：中国人民大学“一人一栈”训练平台。该平台是一个传输协议的训练平台，旨在通过实践加深学生对计算机网络、传输控制协议的理解。平台包括完整的用户模块、日志管理、管理员模块和任务队列等功能，用户可提交自己设计的算法用于评测。具体来说，平台测评核心模块用户态协议框架Transhub基于UDP协议进行实现，提供传输协议基本的功能模块，如序号、包类型、确认机制等，并提供如发送、接收等预制的接口API。 用户需要在该框架上，修改controller.cc代码中的内容，实现一个拥塞控制算法，尽可能地提高网络性能。平台通过模拟不同的网络环境， 并针对丢包、时延和吞吐量三个维度进行综合评分，对用户提供的拥塞控制算法进行评估。
Transhub: The &amp;ldquo;One Person, One Stack&amp;rdquo; Training Platform at Renmin University of China. This platform serves as a training environment for transmission protocols, designed to deepen students&#39; understanding of computer networks and transmission control protocols through hands‑on practice. It includes comprehensive functional modules such as user management, log administration, administrator controls, and task queues, allowing users to submit their own designed algorithms for evaluation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>