<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LitongLab</title>
    <link>https://www.litonglab.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LitongLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.litonglab.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>TACK</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/tack/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: TACK
[Github] [Slide] Abstract
The shared nature of the wireless medium induces contention between data transport and backward signaling, such as acknowledgement. The current way of TCP acknowledgment induces control overhead which is counter-productive for TCP performance especially in wireless local area network (WLAN) scenarios. In this paper, we present a new acknowledgement called TACK (&amp;ldquo;Tame ACK&amp;rdquo;), as well as its TCP implementation TCP-TACK. TCP-TACK works on top of commodity WLAN, delivering high wireless transport goodput with minimal control overhead in the form of ACKs, without any hardware modification.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/art/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Art
[Github] [A demo application] Abstract
Packet losses significantly impact the user experience of wide-area applications such as content distribution and remote procedure call (RPC) based services. However, our production network measurement studies show that the legacy loss recovery is far from satisfactory due to the wide-area loss characteristics (i.e., dynamics and burstiness) in the wild. In this paper, we propose a sender-side Adaptive ReTransmission scheme, ART, which minimizes the recovery time of lost packets with minimal redundancy cost.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blender</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/blender/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: Blender
[Github] [A demo application] Abstract
In the widely used Bluetooth Low-Energy (BLE) neighbor discovery, the parameter configuration of neighbor discovery directly decides the results of the trade-off between discovery latency and power consumption. Therefore, it requires evaluating whether any given parameter configuration meets the demands. The existing solutions, however, are far from satisfactory due to unsolved issues.
Blender, a simulation framework that produces a determined and full probabilistic distribution of discovery latency for a given parameter configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FiND</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/projects/find/</guid>
      <description>Project Name: FiND
[Github] Abstract
FiND is a novel neighbor discovery protocol that accelerates BLE neighbor discovery via Wi-Fi fingerprints without any hardware modifications. The design rationale of FiND is that the two modes of WiFi and BLE show complementarity in both wireless interference and discovery pattern. When abstracting the neighbor discovery problem, this demonstration provides validation for the approach of reasoning-based presence detection in the real world.
Reference
Tong Li, Bowen Hu, Guanjie Tu, Jinwen Shuai, Jiaxin Liang, Yukuan Ding, Ziwei Li, Ke Xu: Accelerating BLE Neighbor Discovery via Wi-Fi Fingerprints.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/about/</guid>
      <description>LitongLab Introduction Basic introduction LitongLab is a research lab led by Professor Li Tong at Renmin University of China. Our main research areas include wireless networks, wired networks, and data center networks.
Wireless networks: Wireless networks are networks that use wireless signals for communication. They are convenient, as they allow access to the network from any location without the need for cables. Wired networks: Wired networks are networks that use cables to connect devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/news/</guid>
      <description>News 2023.10.25 Our paper is accepted by IEEE WISE.
2023.09.07 Our paper is accepted by 中国网络大会.
2023.08.01 实验室成员获得第九届中国国际“互联网 + ”大学生创新创业大赛北京赛区复赛产业命题赛道三等奖。
2023.07.03 Our paper is accepted by ICNP 2023.
2023.07.07 Our two papers are accepted by SIGCOMM&#39;23 Poster and Demos.
2023.06.26 实验室成员获得2023年“中国高校计算机大赛—网络技术挑战赛（A-ST）”三等奖。 成员：杨兆棋（大二）、曹景堃（大二）、杨艺琳（大二）、胡博文（大二）
2023.03.29 Our paper is accepted by 软件学报.
2023.02.11 Our paper is accepted by IEEE INFOCOM Demo 2023.
2023.02.06 Our paper is accepted by IEEE Communications Magazine.
2022.12.06 实验室成员获得2022 年“中国高校计算机大赛—智能交互创新赛”全国总决赛三等奖。 成员：蒋岱均（大二）、曹思源 （大三）、杨兆棋（大二）、刘威（研一）</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/people/</guid>
      <description>Header Dr. Tong Li
Associate Professor @ Renmin University of China, Prior Chief Engineer @ Huawei, PhD @ Tsinghua UniversityPhD Students DuLing Xu (PhD student since 2022) Master Students Zegang Sun(master student since 2023) Xu Yan (master student since 2023) Yang Zi(master student since 2023) Wei Liu (master student since 2022) Shangwen Jiang (master student since 2022) Xinyu Ma (master student since 2022) Shuaipeng Zhu (master student since 2022) Shuoru Yuan (master student since 2022) Undergraduate Students Bowen Hu (undergraduate student since 2021) Zhaoqi Yang (undergraduate student since 2021) Jingkun Cao (undergraduate student since 2021) Yilin Yang (undergraduate student since 2021) Daijun Jiang (undergraduate student since 2021) Xiongwen Guo (undergraduate student since 2021) Zhongqi Tang (undergraduate student since 2021) Haoyue Li (undergraduate student since 2021) Guanjie Tu (undergraduate student since 2020) Siyuan Cao (undergraduate student since 2020) Yijin Zhu (undergraduate student since 2020) Shuailong Yang (undergraduate student since 2019) Yiming Gao (undergraduate student since 2019) Liang Ma (undergraduate student since 2019) Peiyu Zhao (undergraduate student since 2022) Yaoping Luo (undergraduate student since 2022) Annual Group Photo @ 2023 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.litonglab.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.litonglab.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>Conference Papers Tong Li, Jiaxin Liang, Yukuan Ding, Kai Zheng, Xu Zhang, Ke Xu: On Design and Performance of Offline Finding Network. IEEE International Conference on Computer Communications (INFOCOM), pp. 1-10, 2023.05.17. [paper]
Tong Li, Bowen Hu, Guanjie Tu, Jinwen Shuai, Jiaxin Liang, Yukuan Ding, Ziwei Li, Ke Xu: Accelerating BLE Neighbor Discovery via Wi-Fi Fingerprints. IEEE International Conference on Computer Communications (INFOCOM Demo), pp. 1-2, 2023.05.17. [paper]
Yukuan Ding, Tong Li, Jiaxin Liang, Dan Wang: Blender: Toward Practical Simulation Framework for BLE Neighbor Discovery.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>