<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>LitongLab</title>
    <link>https://litonglab.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on LitongLab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://litonglab.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>First Project</title>
      <link>https://litonglab.github.io/projects/first_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://litonglab.github.io/projects/first_project/</guid>
      <description>This is a clock
this is our first project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://litonglab.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://litonglab.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>LitongLab Introduction Basic introduction LitongLab is a research lab led by Professor Li Tong at Renmin University of China. Our main research areas include wireless networks, wired networks, and data center networks.
Wireless networks: Wireless networks are networks that use wireless signals for communication. They are convenient, as they allow access to the network from any location without the need for cables. Wired networks: Wired networks are networks that use cables to connect devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News</title>
      <link>https://litonglab.github.io/news/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://litonglab.github.io/news/</guid>
      <description>2022 2022.12.02: Our paper is accepted by IEEE INFOCOM 2023. 2022.11.16: Our paper is published in CCCF. 2022.08.15: Our paper is accepted by ACM MSWiM 2022. 2022.07.15: Our paper is accepted by IEEE/ACM Transactions on Networking. 2022.06.22: Our paper is accepted by ACM SIGCOMM 2022 Workshop. 2022.03.07: Two of our papers are accepted by IEEE WoWMoM 2022​. 2020 2020.08.13: Gave a talk in the ACM SIGCOMM, which was held virtually (online).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://litonglab.github.io/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://litonglab.github.io/people/</guid>
      <description>LitongLab Members Welcome to LitongLab! We are a team of researchers who are committed to pushing the boundaries of technology. Our members come from diverse backgrounds and bring a wealth of knowledge and expertise to the group. The following is a list of our current members, along with links to their personal websites and GitHub profiles:
Leaders Dr. Alice Smith = | Dr. Bob Johnson - Personal Website | GitHub Masters Ms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://litonglab.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://litonglab.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications Journal Articles &amp;ldquo;Paper 1 Title,&amp;rdquo; by Author 1 and Author 2, Journal Name, January 2020. &amp;ldquo;Paper 2 Title,&amp;rdquo; by Author 3, Journal Name, March 2021. Conference Articles &amp;ldquo;Paper 3 Title,&amp;rdquo; by Author 1 and Author 3, Conference Name, April 2021. Patents &amp;ldquo;Patent 1,&amp;rdquo; by Inventor 1, Application Date: January 2019, Grant Date: December 2020. &amp;ldquo;Patent 2,&amp;rdquo; by Inventor 2 and Inventor 3, Application Date: February 2020, Grant Date: October 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>